now sinjin is also in focus nimesh is
standing by to tell us why dimishai aye
vishan said there's going to be a large
block in sinjin today morning uh so
bicon is looking to sell up to five
percent stake uh in sinjin by block deal
double codes launched last night uh the
indicative price is around five percent
discount from yesterday's closing price
so the base price is 550 uh uh up to 573
so in between that the the block will be
done uh in terms of demand i i believe
uh a mix of domestic as well as some big
global funds are likely to participate
in today's blog deal so a big block uh
to start with as engine will open in the
red because there is a there is a large
block and a bit of a discount but uh
maybe it will recover uh you know uh
intraday post the block is done also
there is a 90 day lock up now for buy
control for the stake remember biocon
owns uh close to 70 and the initial
feedback was uh that they were looking
to sell 10 odd percent stake but this is
only half block that they're doing so
maybe even if they want to sell further
it will be on our post 90 days only and
as i said there is a good mix of demand
from both domestic and global investors
so watch out first engine in the in the
in the start may open red but may
recover as well uh given that you know
the stock ended three percent lower
yesterday and there was an anticipation
of a block coming so bit of short as
well on the stock so maybe you'll see a
bit of covering as well after the block
is done